# Veronicah Anzimbu

**LANGUAGES**: English +2547 40875071

<u>veronicahanzimbu@gmail.com</u>

in linkedin.com/in/Veronicah Anzimbu

https://www.linkedin.com/in/veronicah-anzimbu-aa15a8232

Nairobi Kenya

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Results-oriented a computer science professional with excellent technical ability who understands how to gather user requirements, conduct tests, assess risks, and fix issues. Data scientists have experience gathering, arranging, and utilizing information from both technical and non-technical employees. I am a proficient security analyst and data interpreter. Being an experienced troubleshooter, I have excellent attention to detail, exceptional system security diagnosis, and repair skills, both proactive and passive. The ability to accurately manage multiple activities at once, find and maintain a full-time employment that presents professional difficulties, and use excellent communication, cyber security, data science, time-management, and problem-solving skills in the workplace. Interests include machine learning, Al, system analysis, and data science in general.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

March 2023 - Currently Freelancer - FREELANCING Nairobi - Kenya

- Troubleshot IT systems maintenance issues
- Pen-testing
- CTF challenges
- Constructed deep learning models and scalable machine learning systems.
- API generation

March 2023 – July 2024 Data Scientist – PATHWAYS TECHNOLOGIES Nairobi – Kenya

November 2022 - January 2023

Machine Learning Intern – GEARBOX Nairobi –Kenya

- Machine learning frameworks Tensor flow , Sk learn, Tensorflowjs, pytorch
- API and endpoint generation using modelbit and local endpoint with flask, streamlite and fast api.
- Creating user interface of the machine learning using flutter, js, css and html.
- Machine learning frameworks Tensor flow, Sk learn
- API generation
- Performed installation, maintenance and repair for complex internal computer hardware and various software applications.
- Partnered with engineering staff on identifying and resolving interface issues.
  - Implemented IT machine learning model
  - Modeling (setting up models), Cleaning datasets, Getting insights on data
  - Setting up and deployment of datasets
  - Tensor flow frameworks Image segmentation

May 2022- November 2022

Machine learning and data science-Intern – TAMBUA

## health org

## **February 2021 –April 2021** Attaché- ICT- Kinyanjui Nairobi, Kenya

- Adept knowledge of the artificial intelligence field.
- Built predictive, deep learning models and machine-learning algorithms to analyze large data sets.
- Performed installation, maintenance and repair for complex internal computer hardware and various software applications
- Performed troubleshooting to correct computer hardware and software malfunctions
- Assessed system hardware and software and suggested modifications to reduce lag time and improve overall speed
  - Used diagnostic tools to identify hardware failures
  - Responded to support requests from end-users EDUCATION
  - Completed set up tasks for institution, including installing and configuring PCs, phones and printers.
  - Diagnosed and resolved hardware, software and application faults to maintain stability.

# CORE QUALIFICATIONS AND SKILLS

- Data Mining
  Pen-testing
  Forensic analysis
  SQL injection
  Google colab
  PYTHON scripting
  JavaScript
  - Data Visualization
    Maths Expertise
    Systems Analysis
    SQL
    Flutter
    Html, css
- Technical WritingTechnical Analysis
- Network
   TroubleshootingTeam worker
- Good communication tools

#### **EDUCATION**

Sept 2018 –Mar 2023	Bachelor of Science in computer science	Meru university of science and technology	Second class upper division.
Mar 2024 –Jul 2024	Certification in Data science	Pathways Technologies and Konza Technologies	Passed.
Sept 2018 –Mar 2023	Certification in Cyber Security Analyst	Cyber Shujaa, USIU	Passed.
Jan 2014 – Nov 2017	KCSE	Bushiangala sec school	B(plain)

NMAP scanning

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

2024: **Machine Data Science**, Pathways Technologies

2024:**Security Analyst Specialist**, Cyber
Shujaa

2022: **Data Analytics** & Science, Skill up

2023:**Power BI**, Great Learning

2023:**JavaScript & React.js** – Devtown, Google

2023:**Tinder clone – Devtown**, Google 2023:**Harry potter invisibility-** Devtown , Google

2023:**Node.js and Express-** Devtown

#### **REFERENCES**

Dr.Amos Chege- Meru university akirongo@must.ac.ke +254720984636 Pharis mavia pharismavia@gmail.com +25708219378 Erick Kirima- Tambua Health eric@tambuahealth.com +254743169027